University Advancement Division Records UA043
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Special events records, 2007 -- 2013; UA043.006; 2.66 Linear Feet; 4 Digital Object(s)
  - Friedman School 30th Anniversary, 2010 November 6; UA043.006.016.00087; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 87)
  - Alvin Howell Professorship, 2010 December 9; UA043.006.016.00088; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 88)
  - Los Angeles Campaign Celebration, 2011 January 23; UA043.006.016.00089; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 89)
  - Hong Kong Campaign Celebration, 2011 January 26; UA043.006.016.00090; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 90)
  - Schmidheiny Professorship in International Business, 2011 February 16; UA043.006.016.00091; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 91)
  - New York Campaign Celebration, 2011 February 24; UA043.006.016.00092; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 92)
  - Granoff Music Presentation Joshua Bell, 2011 February 26; UA043.006.016.00093; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 93)
  - Miami Campaign Celebration, 2011 March 4; UA043.006.016.00094; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 94)
  - Palm Beach Campaign Celebration, 2011 March 5; UA043.006.016.00095; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 95)
  - London Campaign Celebration, 2011 March 26; UA043.006.016.00096; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 96)
  - Washington DC Campaign Celebration, 2011 April 4; UA043.006.016.00097; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 97)
  - Solomont Lecture Pelosi, 2011 April 8; UA043.006.016.00098; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 98)
  - Tisch Athletic Groundbreaking, 2011 April 12; UA043.006.016.00099; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 99)
  - Tufts Financial Network, 2011 April 13; UA043.006.016.00100; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 100)
  - Snyder Presidential Lecture, 2011 April 25; UA043.006.016.00101; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 101)
  - Annual Real Estate Luncheon, 2011 May 6; UA043.006.016.00102; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 102)
  - Neuroscience Ambassador Day, 2011 May 20; UA043.006.016.00103; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 103)
  - Charles Tufts Society Luncheon, 2011 May 19; UA043.006.016.00104; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 104)
  - Tufts Night at Pops, 2011 May 19; UA043.006.016.00105; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 105)
  - New England Campaign Celebration, 2011 May 20; UA043.006.016.00106; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 106)
  - President's Reception Parents Weekend, 2011 May 21; UA043.006.016.00107; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 107)
  - President Bacow Celebration, 2011 June 2; UA043.006.016.00108; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 108)
  - Alumni Weekend, 2011 May 19 -- 22; UA043.006.016.00109; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 109)
  - San Francisco Campaign Celebration, 2011 June 4; UA043.006.016.00110; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 110)
  - Tufts Young Alumni Reception, 2011 June 11; UA043.006.016.00111; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 111)
  - 2011 August, UA043.006.017.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - 2011 September, UA043.006.017.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - 2011 October, UA043.006.017.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - 2011 November, UA043.006.017.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - 2011 December, UA043.006.017.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - 2012 February, UA043.006.017.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - 2012 March, UA043.006.017.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - 2012 April, UA043.006.017.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - 2012 May, UA043.006.017.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - 2012 June, UA043.006.017.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Communications projects records, 2011 -- 2013; UA043.006.018.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - International Parents Reception invitation, 2012 August; UA043.006.018.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - FY2013 invitations and programs, 2012 -- 2013; UA043.006.018.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Alumni, donor relations, and event marketing materials, circa 2011 -- 2013; UA043.006.018.00004; 22 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 4-25)
  - Solomont Lecture fliers and poster, 2013 April; UA043.006.018.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Blank Tufts embossed cards, circa 2011 -- 2012; UA043.006.018.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Association of Tufts Alumnae Centennial Celebration, 2005; UA043.006.00001
    Powerpoint presentation of ATA Centennial Celebration.
- Audiovisual materials, circa 2000 -- 2009; UA043.007; 0.75 Linear Feet; 26 Digital Object(s)
  These materials preserve their received arrangement.
  This series contains audiovisual materials of events and presentations held at Tufts. Events covered include the "Teaching at Tufts after 9/11" lecture by Sol Gittleman, 2004 commencement, and the dedication of the Granoff Music Center. The lecture by Sol Gittleman, the dedication of the Granoff Music Center, and the presentation concerning the Beyond Boundaries campaign exist in multiple formats. Materials date circa 2002-2009.
  - Sol Gittleman - Teaching at Tufts after 9/11, 2004; UA043.007.019.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 1)
    DVD
  - 2004 and So Much More: Tufts Commencement, UA043.007.019.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Tufts Friedman School of Nutrition Video CD, 2005-12-05; UA043.007.019.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Connecting Fletcher and You, 2006; UA043.007.019.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Special Announcement and Celebration Honoring the Leadership and Generosity of Trustee Jonathan M. Tisch, A'76, 2006; UA043.007.019.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Beyond Boundaries CDs, 2006 November 3; UA043.007.019.00006; 1 Folder(s); 4 Digital Object(s) (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Isn't This a Lovely Day: Dedication of the Perry and Marty Granoff Music Center, 2007-02-09; UA043.007.019.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Beyond Boundaries Wang Center tapes, 2006 November 3; UA043.007.020.00001; 4 Video Recordings (Box 20)
    4 Panasonic DVCPro 126L tapes
  - Granoff Dedication tapes, 2007 February 9 -- 12; UA043.007.020.00002; 4 Video Recordings; 7 Digital Object(s) (Box 20)
    SONY DVCAM tapes
  - Granoff Dedication mini DV cassettes, 2007 February 9; UA043.007.020.00003; 5 Video Recordings; 5 Digital Object(s) (Box 20)
    SONY mini DV cassettes
  - Granoff: guided tour, 2007; UA043.007.00002
  - Granoff: hitting a high note, 2007; UA043.000315
  - Granoff: special delivery, 2007; UA043.000316
  - Sol Gittleman's Teaching at Tufts After 9/11 lecture tapes, circa 2004; UA043.007.021.00001; 2 Video Recordings (Box 21)
    VHSs
  - Sol Gittleman tapes, circa 2000s; UA043.007.021.00002; 2 Video Recordings (Box 21)
  - Tufts Bhangra Dance Music, 1994-12-31 -- 2006-11-03; UA043.007.00001
    One song of Bhangra dance music.